weather services using words like potentially historic crippling and catastrophic to describe the approaching ice storm across the South suffice to say
使用像潜在的历史沉重的和灾难性的词语来形容整个南方足矣即将到来的冰灾说气象服务
defecting Millions
百万叛逃
America's sweetheart one of the greats is the child star turned public servant and diplomat tonight we remember the legendary Shirley Temple nightly news
美国甜心的伟人之一，是童星变成公务员和外交官今晚我们还记得传说中的秀兰·邓波晚间新闻
NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams reporting tonight from the Olympic Winter Games in Sochi Russia
NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯从冬奥会在俄罗斯的索契今晚报告
good evening and from here at the Olympic Winter Games Wii began back home tonight with an e normous winter storm here's how forecasters at the National Weather Service describe what is sliding up from the southwest to the northeast quotes
晚上好，并从在此间举行的冬季奥运会的Wii开始回家今晚与电子normous冬季风暴这里的预报员在国家气象局怎么形容从西南向上滑动到东北报价
confidence is increasing in an event of historical proportions prepare now for this potentially crippling event
信心是增加的比例历史事件现在准备这个潜在的破坏性事件
here is the map to night of the individual counties that are under watches and warnings
这里是地图是根据手表和警告的个别县的夜
it's a rain snow and ice off and put its the ice they really fear will be crippling tonight or standing up hurricane hunter aircraft to look at it from aloft
这是一个雨雪和冰关闭，把它的他们真正害怕的冰将是沉重今晚或站立飓风猎人飞机看它从高处
93 million Americans in the path of this one there r States of America in C in 5 different southern states including Georgia so hard
9300万美国人在这其中的路径有ř美国以C国5个不同的南部各州，包括乔治亚这么难
buy that last snowfall we have it all covered for you tonight Al Roker is here with us but first a mark Potter in Atlanta that starts of a marketing mix
买，去年降雪便拥有了一切为您承保今晚铝罗克是在我们这里，但第一标记波特在亚特兰大的营销组合，开头
the bad weather is no expected to hit
恶劣的天气并没有预计将达到
sometime early tomorrow morning the only good news is that allows officials in Resident just a little more time
有时明天一早唯一的好消息是，允许在驻地官员只是多一点时间
part of a message to avoid what happen 2 weeks ago 12 point 6 inches of snow
消息，以避免发生什么2个星期前12点6英寸积雪的一部分
is being worn the storm heading to morrow morning could be long remembered
正在穿的风暴前往明天早上能长久记住
Travel is going to be impossible if this is going to be a catastrophic event for the areas in purple
旅游将是不可能的，如果这将是紫色灾难性事件的地区
mini trees is the major threat
迷你树是主要威胁
this is one of mother nature's worst kinds of storms that can be inflicted on
这是大自然的最恶劣的暴风雨中，可以对造成一
South Carolina causing major outages
南卡罗来纳州造成重大停电
repair Cruise have already been brought in from around the country what's a little more sophisticated Richard Mendoza Atlanta Public Works commissioner says pending ice on the roads is especially dangerous it makes driving treacherous you can I get traction you can control your vehicle
维修克鲁斯已经带来了来自全国各地的什么是多了几分成熟的理查德·门多萨亚特兰大工务专员表示，在道路上挂起冰是它让驾驶奸诈你我可以得到牵引你可以控制你的车辆特别是危险的
we are strong advising our residents to stay off the roads in telecommute were possible today
我们强烈建议我们的居民留在道路今天在家中是可能的
7 hours stuck in his car during last month paralyzing store
在上个月瘫痪店卡在他的车7小时
house and not on the highway are side drive
房子，而不是在高速公路上的侧驱动
in my truck and stocking up grocery store shut down power goes off I'm going to be at work
在我的卡车和年货的杂货店关闭电源中断，我要在工作
string of crashes on icy roads around causing at least 4 fatalities
在结冰的道路交通事故造成周围至少4人死亡字符串
in Mississippi snow and ice drive trucks of the roads in North and South Carolina kids home after heavy snow for schools to close
在北美和南卡罗来纳州的孩子回家的道路密西西比冰雪驱动卡车大雪后学校关闭
classes in Georgia what's new on the northern counties Kimberly force the closure of i-75 a major highway
类在格鲁吉亚有什么新的县北部金佰利强制的I-75的主要公路关闭
when are you considered not that many people are on the Roses a heater warnings for all softener to stock up on things such as heating fuel batteries for radios and flashlights and medication enuff to write out this storm
当你认为没有那么多的人都对玫瑰加热器警告所有柔软剂囤积的东西，如取暖燃料电池的收音机和手电筒和药物ENUFF写出来这场风暴
Aramark Potter setting this scene in Atlanta mark thanks as I mentioned Al Roker here with us working evening shift tonight did somebody say footage of snow in Washington DC by Friday night
爱玛客波特设置这样的场景在亚特兰大庆祝感谢为我所提到的Al Roker大在我们这里工作的夜班，今晚也有人说雪在华盛顿片段在星期五晚上
very possible to get finished with the South but in the meantime we're going to be looking at brutal conditions from Dallas
很可能得到完成了南方，但在此期间，我们将要寻找从达拉斯残酷的条件
Fort Worth all the way up in the New England have a wife swap of ice storm warning from Atlanta in the South Carolina and this winter storm watch and winter storm warning go all the way up in the ears what we got setting up basically we're looking at low pressure developing how long a stationary front both
沃斯堡了所有的方式，在新英格兰有冰暴从亚特兰大在南卡罗来纳州警告的妻子交换，这冬季风暴手表和冬季风暴预警一路走在耳边我们得到了什么设置，基本上我们看着低压发展静止锋多久既
the double barrel over the Gulf in the end of the Carolina coast
双桶海湾上空的卡罗来纳州海岸的结束
and what we got gold Moisture coming up out of the south meeting up with cold bitter cold air coming out of the north
而我们得到了金牌水分上来了南方的满足了从北方的寒冷严寒的空气
how long that battle on we're seeing eye for ready South Carolina some places third of an inch of ice this isn mixture will continue looking for as far as accumulation and this is critical it is between Atlanta and make it up to 2 inches of ice
在我们那场战役所看到的冰一寸多长眼准备南卡罗来纳州一些地方，第三这个ISN混合物将继续寻找尽可能的积累，这是关键的是亚特兰大之间，并使其达到2英寸厚的冰
is extenze all the way down to central Georgia on in the Carolinas continues up in the South Carolina and this is the major airport delays Square telling people stay off the road and as the system continues up the coast if you look at this blue line in our future cast
是extenze一路下跌到格鲁吉亚中央在卡罗来纳州继续在南卡罗来纳州，这是主要的机场延误广场告诉人们躲开了道路，为系统继续沿海岸向北，如果你看这个蓝色的线在我们的未来投
that's the Wayne snow on the freezing rain snow line in depending on where this is going to set up we could be looking at massive amounts of snow in Sacramento tweaking me the mouth
这是在冻雨雪线韦恩雪不同的地方，这是要建立，我们可以寻找在萨克拉门托大量的雪扭捏我的嘴
as we go on during the day over the next 24 hours Richard Atlanta 8 inches in Charlotte that we got to the North Washington DC possibly 7 inches to a foot Bryan and summaries even to the north and west of that up to a foot and a half of snow
因为我们白天在接下来的24小时理查德亚特兰大去8英寸夏洛特，我们到了北华盛顿特区可能7英寸到脚Bryan和总结甚至到了北部和西部达一英尺半雪
this is gonna be tough when will stay on it will see you in the morning I think for being here with us tonight and now these games and you will see some of this and primetime coverage tonight this next result was blasted around the world as urgent news earlier today
这会是艰难的，当将留在它会看到你在早晨，我认为今晚，现在这些游戏是在我们这里，你会看到一些今晚这和黄金时段报道这下结果被世界各地的炮轰为紧急新闻今天早些时候
snowboarder Shaun White will go home from his third Olympic Games without a metal this time in the men's halfpipe in fact it's a team USA
滑雪运动员肖恩·怀特将回家从他的第三个奥运无金属这一次在男子半管，其实这是一个美国队
shutout in a sport invented in the US just part of the news from here and Thompson is up to the mountain top ski venue for us tonight
完封在美国发明从这里和汤普森的新闻只是部分的运动是到山顶的滑雪场地，我们今晚
good evening Brian today the Winter Olympics felt like this spring game sports in official to cancel the practice runs for the women's downhill and creating a backdrop for one of the biggest upsets apps games so far
晚上好今天布莱恩冬奥会感觉就像在官方今年春季的体育比赛，取消实践运行的妇女下坡，创造一个背景为最大的冷门之一，应用程式游戏至今
Benny's today's weather what's the toughest competitor across country
Benny的今天的天气是什么全国各地的最棘手的竞争对手
free sprit and more like a demolition derby gear stumbling on snow turn to mush you but 40 degree temperatures it was just what is mashed potato snow conditions and design complaints played the men's snowboard halfpipe
自由精神，而更像一个爆破德比齿轮绊脚石雪转玉米粥你，但40度的温度这只是什么是土豆泥雪况和设计投诉扮演的男子单板滑雪半管
what one fan script full
一个粉丝脚本全
making the final Shaun White
使得最终肖恩怀特
the wish that the cancer survivor to the Olympics with his family can you stay up until the very end and now he wants to grow up to be an engineer or snowboarders
该癌症幸存者奥运会与他的家人，你可以留起来，直到最后一刻，现在他想长大后成为一名工程师或滑雪的愿望
what are you going to tell your friends about this is variance in the back to St Louis I got to me John White
你有什么要告诉你这个朋友是方差的回圣路易斯我得到了我的约翰·怀特
that didn't happen whitelist empty handed
这并没有发生白名单空手而归
what the US did have a reason to celebrate today Erin Hamlin orange America's first medals ever in singles luge women's ski jumping made its Olympic debut at the first gear to jump Park Cities Sarah Hendrickson
是美国确实有一个理由庆祝今天艾琳哈姆林橙美国的第一个金牌曾经在单打无舵雪橇女子跳台滑雪在第一轮跳公园城市莎拉亨德里克森做了它的首次亮相奥运
meaning of the top we on New York a moment just to be a part of it and something to be proud of
顶部我们在纽约意义的时刻只是要它和一件值得骄傲的一部份
don't get any more gold in Canadian skier Alex Bilodeau brother Frederic
不要在加拿大滑雪选手亚历克斯碧萝弟弟弗雷德里克任何更多的黄金
consecutive gold medal in Mobile another wonderful moment for the brothers Bilodeau
连续的金牌移动另一个美妙的时刻为兄弟碧萝
Rick who has cerebral palsy is Alex's inspiration
里克谁拥有脑瘫是Alex的灵感
I want him as close as possible to me when I when I when is the big one like that makea and live that moment with M
我希望他尽可能地接近我，当我当我的时候是大的像MAKEA和生活的那一刻以M
and as for tomorrow at looks like the weather will continue to be a big story temperatures could climb as high is 50 degrees on the mountain
并以此为明天貌似天气将继续成为一个大的故事气温可能爬上高是在山上50度
Ann Thompson of the mountain top venues with all things Winter Games and thanks we have an update tonight on what was our lives story last night this dangerous of accusation going on in the embattled Syrian city of homes today the head of American intelligence
山顶场地与万物冬奥会，并感谢安·汤普森我们有一个更新今晚对什么是我们的生命故事，昨晚这个危险的指控，今天要在四面楚歌的叙利亚城市家园美国情报首长的
set the war and the humanitarian crisis had created what he called an apocalyptic disaster there be a vacuolation Africa is expected to resume tomorrow
集战争和人道主义危机已经创造了他所谓的世界末日的灾难会有一个非洲空泡形成，预计明日恢复
we learned of a big lost today and perhaps the best way to put it is this somewhere right now someone is ordering a Shirley Temple welearn today that Shirley Temple has died at the age of 85
我们今天学的一大失落，或许把它最好的办法就是这个地方，现在有人在今天订购秀兰·邓波welearn的秀兰邓波儿已经在85岁去世
she was America's favorite movie star during the Depression era the 1930s a little girl who gave her country a big left when it really needed that she was king
她是美国的大萧条时期最喜欢的电影明星1930谁给她的国家大左，当它真正需要的，她是国王的小女孩
the president for it in later years she became Shirley Temple black and became a public servant and a pioneer we can look back tonight from NBC's Kate snow
在以后的几年总统吧，她成为秀兰邓波儿的黑色，并成为公务员的先驱，我们今晚可以回头从NBC的凯特雪
we can
我们可以
is the song we all think of
是大家都认为的歌
Cummins so many
康明斯这么多
pictures in almost before she was just 12
图片中是12几乎在她
Shirley Temple with her golden Realty
秀兰邓波儿与她的金色置业
pressing times in the 1930s giving America a reason to smile
按倍，在20世纪30年代美国给予一个微笑的理由
who came this cheerful irresistible little girl who could sing and dance into everything seemingly and she make people feel good
谁进来谁可以唱歌跳舞到一切看似这欢快的不可抗拒的小女孩，她让人们感觉良好
she left it there spirits
她离开那里烈酒
time when segregation was still the norm tshirt the screen with
当时种族隔离仍是常态T恤的屏幕，
dildo jangles Robinson and called him
假阳具叮当作响的罗宾逊和打电话给他
favorite color star has a child stars who made millions but as she grew up her movie career faded setting the stage for remarkable second act
最喜欢的颜色有明星谁赚了几百万一个童星，但因为她长大了她的电影生涯褪色的设置阶段为显着的第二幕
field President Nixon made her his un representative in 1972 she spoke bluntly about her own breasts
尼克松总统现场做了她自己的驻联合国代表于1972年，她直言不讳地谈到她自己的乳房
search for the recommendation Road interests should be removed
搜索建议道利益应该被删除
simple mastectomy
单纯乳房切除术
summer hospital bed sheets women to have mammogram
夏天的医院床单妇女有乳房X光检查
strange lump in your breast during anal
在肛门肿块怪在你的乳房
symptoms to be afraid
症状害怕
to go to the doctor to 100 to the diplomat ambassador to Ghana and leader
要去看医生，以100到外交官驻加纳和领导者
public servant an advocate married for 55 years
公务员结婚55年的倡导者
is Sean Penn
是西恩潘
star quality is timeless and that's what she is she's times and the most famous child actresses of all time
恒星的质量是永恒的，这就是她是她的时代和所有时代最有名的女演员童
Kate snow NBC News New York
凯特雪NBC新闻纽约
Emily come back here tonight Bladimir Putin's big show
艾米丽回来今晚Bladimir普京大秀
the most expensive Olympics ever how a president who rules with something of an iron fist transform the city by the sea say nothing of this country
最昂贵的一届奥运会如何总统谁的东西的铁腕统治改造城市在海边什么都不说这个国家的
Bakery in Sochi for the first few days of these games we have the great luxury a being able to travel around here was one of the leading American experts on Russia and tonight with his health
糕点店在索契这些游戏的最初几天，我们有很大的奢侈品能在这里周游是一个在俄罗斯领先的美国专家，今晚与他的健康状况
we have a look at this bold move what really is a 50 billion dollar Best Buy flat Amir Putin that he could pull off this event and welcome the world to this place
我们来看看这个大胆的举动，真正是50十亿美元的百思买平阿米尔普京，他可以拉断此事件，并欢迎世界到这个地方
like a lot of past Olympics this is really to Olympics at different altitudes there's this Stadium events beneath the flame down along the Black Sea and was called the coastal cluster of venues then about 25 miles away there are the skiing events in the mountain cluster
像很多过去的奥运会，这是真的奥运会在不同的高度有这个体育场的火焰顺着黑海下方事件，被称为场地沿海集群则约25英里远有中山路集群的滑雪活动
none of it up top down below existed seven years ago
下面没有它自上而下存在七年前
to get between the two the most expensive stretch of road in the world 7 billion
两个最昂贵的一段道路，在世界间拿到7十亿
and everywhere you look there are hotels and restaurants in stores Riverside promenade and it's all brand new
到处都看不过酒店和餐馆在商店滨江长廊和它的所有品牌的新
these days David Remnick is the editor of The New Yorker magazine what he lived here for years he speaks the language Annie's book on Russia won the Pulitzer
这些天，大卫·雷姆尼克是纽约客杂志的编辑什么，他在这里住了几年，他讲的语言安妮的书在俄罗斯赢得了普利策
we traveled up to the mountain venues with him to assess Bladimir Putin's Olympic Games
我们走遍了山上的场地与他评估Bladimir普京的奥运会
what does the world need to know about Bladimir Putin and how should Americans view
是什么世界需要了解Bladimir普京以及如何查看美国
this Russian leader whose going to be around it appears on good law
这家俄罗斯的领袖，他将是围绕它出现在良法
reading questions for the same time criticized anyway to lease a human rights issues
阅读的同时批评的问题反正租用一个人权问题
send contacts historically what's going on here in 1991 plays it collapsed as an ideology eclectus Empire and self-confidence shot at love message for years
发送联系人历史上这是怎么回事就在1991年扮演倒塌作为一种意识形态折衷帝国和自信枪击爱的讯息多年
and they were democratic movements but a company has the longest case of the missing man and he's all about stability in development that appeal to Russian and very populated
而且他们的民主运动，但公司有上述失踪男子的最长的情况下，他的所有关于稳定发展，吸引俄罗斯和人口极
like this can stand
这样可以站
50 billion dollars openly and get away with this in the sky
公开50十亿美元，逃脱这个在天空
is the weather doing his parents this is his greatest lead his people is granite Construction maybe criticizing you want to see in the West younger critics in Russia today
是天气做他的父母，这是他的人是花岗岩建筑也许批评你今天要看到在西方年轻批评家在俄罗斯他最大的铅
what is a great appeal when the games are gone watch this to remain as an international ski resort he said recently is hoping for tourists
什么是一个很大的吸引力消失的游戏都看这个保持作为国际滑雪场，他最近说，当希望游客
Europe in the US even China and just like holding the game Siri it's something of a gamble given the threat of terrorism across the mountains from here
在欧洲，美国甚至中国，只是喜欢抱着游戏Siri的这件事情从这里给出恐怖主义威胁整个山脉的赌博
Norma Stitz confidence in the village keep the pieces fit that way it looks like a ski resort in its earliest for the moment
诺玛Stitz信心在村里保持件适合的方式，它看起来像一个滑雪胜地，其最早的时刻
Remnick knows the media coverage of toilets in hotel rooms in Sochi glitches is not going over well with the Russians any of these games go off without incident Putin will get what he wants and label them a success knowing the whole world is watching
雷姆尼克知道厕所的媒体报道在酒店房间在索契毛刺不会很好与俄罗斯这些游戏的熄灭没有发生任何事件，普京将得到他想要的东西，并标记他们成功知道整个世界都在注视着
Putin wants respect with an anything else on in the modern world when he sees is a sting hypocritical a knockin
普京希望与上，当他看到当今世界任何其他方面是有刺虚伪敲入一个
angry and remember how down this country was a generation how humiliate it was by the end of the Cold War food is reaction to that
生气，还记得这个国家怎么下来了一代如何羞辱是由冷战时期的食物到底是反应了
are things to David Remick and by the way suck she has other big events coming up after this a g8 summit World Cup soccer in a formula 1 Grand Prix there will be
事情进行到大卫雷米克并顺便吸她已经等大型活动来了这后一个G8峰会世界杯足球赛在一级方程式大奖赛将有
24000 brand new hotel rooms awaiting guess another break we're back in the moment with what the noises all about here in Sochi
24000全新的酒店房间等候猜另一个突破我们回到当下什么噪音所有关于这里在索契
as we are talking you may hear what sounds like the dull roar of a jet dryer in the background when we're on the air the new
因为我们正在谈论你可能会听到什么听起来像喷气机在后台的沉闷的轰鸣声时，我们是在空气中的新
is coming from the Olympic torch and the Russians are clearly making something about torch States
从奥运火炬和俄罗斯未来有明确作出一些有关国家火炬
it's the most powerful we have ever seen at any games it sounds more like a Soyuz rocket blasting off and speaking of space the flame is in
它是最强大的，我们所见过它听起来任何游戏更像是一个联盟号火箭发射升空和口语的空间火焰中
the visible from space are friends on board the International Space Station took this photo of the whole complex on their last pass above us from 220 miles above the earth
从太空可见的是朋友登上国际空间站拍下了这张照片整复对他们的最后一传上我们220英里以上的地球
we have some news tonight about an important member of our family tonight specifically is a long time former anchor of this broadcast in very good friend of ours
我们有一些消息，今晚今晚我们家族的重要成员特别是此广播的非常好的朋友我们很长一段时间前主播
Tom Brokaw is undergoing treatment for multiple myeloma a form of cancer affecting blood cells in the bone marrow he was diagnosed this past summer at the Mayo Clinic dominos doctors are very encouraged about the progress has been making a Skype working all the while
汤姆·布罗考正在接受治疗多发性骨髓瘤的癌症影响血细胞在骨髓中，他被确诊过去的这个夏天在梅奥诊所的医生骨牌形式是非常鼓舞的进展一直在Skype的所有的工作，而
in a public statement released tonight by our network Tom said quote win the support of my family medical team in friends I am very optimistic about the future and look forward to continuing my life my working Adventure still to come
今晚在我们的网络中发布了一个公开声明，称汤姆报价赢得了我的家庭的医疗团队的支持，朋友们，我非常看好未来，期待着继续我的生活我的工作冒险还在后面
Irie Mane the luckiest guy I know I am very grateful for the interest in my condition but I also hope everyone understands I wish to keep this a private matter
入江鬃毛上最幸运的家伙，我知道我很感谢在我的病情的利益，但我也希望每个人都能理解，我想保持这种私事
on a personal note in the Life Goes On Department the Williams is an Brokaw's were the movies together the night before my flight to Russia terms of Tom's continuing workload will be airing some of his reporting as part of our Olympic coverage here later this week
就我个人而言在生活在继续处威廉姆斯是一个布罗考的前我的航班汤姆的持续工作量俄罗斯方面的夜晚是电影一起将播出他的一些报告，作为我们的奥运报道的一部分，在这里一周后
and in an email tonight Tom mentioned at least the possibility
并在一封电子邮件今晚汤姆提到至少有可能
Springsteen tour in Australia just to give Bruce Obama book some atoms publicity cast on a Tuesday night thank you for being here with us on Brian Williams a footnote about primetime coverage tonight that's at 8 7 Central
斯普林斯汀旅游在澳大利亚只给布鲁斯·奥巴马的书的一些原子宣传浇铸在周二晚上谢谢你能在这里和我们布赖恩·威廉斯关于黄金时段覆盖的注脚今晚这是在8 7环
Bob Costas took himself out of the lineup for tonight as he deals with infection Matt Lauer will be your substitute host for this evening
鲍勃·科斯塔斯把自己出的阵容今晚为他处理感染马特·劳尔将是你的替代寄主今天晚上
for Bob we must like Ironman streak of 157 straight primetime Olympics broadcast
鲍勃，我们必须像157直黄金时段播出奥运会铁人三项连胜
what goes back to Barcelona in 92128 back in the game shortly we hope to see you back here tomorrow we die
什么追溯到巴萨在92128后面的比赛不久，我们希望看到你回到这里明天要死了